# Ishara Edirisinghe

429 Frankwood Avenue Thunder Bay, ON P7B 4R3 Cell (807) 707- 6284

E-mail: ishi.avodini@gmail.com

#### **Objective**

A hard-working individual who is looking to secure in a part time job role and seeking for the position of cashier or helping assistant as I have two years of experience in customer service. As a fast-learner I'm prepared to be trained on the job bringing excellent service to customers and the ability to work in a team and relate effectively with other members of the workplace.

### **Education**

Confederation College (Reading) Post Graduate Diploma in ICT solutions for businesses	Thunder Bay, ON	2020-2021
Sri Lanka Institute of Information Technology (SLIIT) BSc. Special (Hons) Degree in Information Technology	Malabe, Sri Lanka	2011-2014

### **Skills**

- Effective team player
- Punctual and can work with minimal guidance
- Clear communication in both written and verbal
- Customer oriented and management skills
- Well organized and professional
- Multitasking
- Willingness to learn

# **Work Experience**

### Frontend Cashier, Safeway, Arthur St., Thunder Bay

2020 April-Present

Currently working as a part time employee providing excellent customer service and maintaining well organized checkout area. Responsibilities include, greeting customers, scan and enter data accurately and answer for inquiries of customers by positively engaging with them.

Global Brand Ambassador, Confederation College, IEC Thunder Bay 2020 Feb – 2020 Mar Worked as a part time employee on campus for one month contract and responsibilities included, help raise the brand awareness and increase sales promoting the college through social media websites. Apart from that organizing events and campaigns and implementing them are also included.

# Fashion and Freedom, Customer Support Representative and Cashier Maharagama, Colombo 2018-2019

Responsibilities included greeting customers, provide better customer service and assist customers with after sales service. Instead of that, responding promptly for customer inquiries, cash handling (at cashier) and generating sales reports weekly are also included.

### SLIIT, Academic Instructor in IT department Colombo, Sri Lanka 2015-2019

Responsibilities included Conduct lab sessions and tutorials for undergraduates based on IT subjects such as programming languages, database management system and networking subjects Evaluate students in project presentations Conduct online exams and viva Marking assignments and online exams. In addition to these general works, attending in research work and involve students for projects is more important.

# **Community Involvement & Volunteer Work**

•	Active member of Interact Club of High School	2009
•	Voluntary worker in Environmental Society SLIIT	2011
•	Active member of Leo Club in Sri Lanka	2013
•	Vice President - Rotaract Club of SLIIT	2015
•	Volunteering group at Confederation College	2020

### <u>Availability</u>

Monday	Tuesday	Wednesday	Thursday	Friday	Saturday	Sunday
	Available from 7.00 a.m. to 3.00 p.m.	N/A	Full day Available	Full day Available	Full day Available	Full day Available
Available from 4.00 p.m. onwards	N/A	N/A				

# References

Can provide upon Request